<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:padding="16dp">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:padding="16dp">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/title"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="About Our Weather App"
            android:textSize="24sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"/>

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/info"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Welcome to our weather app! Our goal is to provide you with accurate and up-to-date weather information so you can plan your day effectively.\n\nKey Features:\n\nReal-Time Updates: Get the latest weather conditions in real-time.\nHourly Forecasts: Plan your activities with hourly weather forecasts.\nDaily Forecasts: Stay prepared with detailed daily weather predictions.\nCustomizable Alerts: Set personalized weather alerts for your locations.\nInteractive Maps: Visualize weather patterns with interactive maps.\nWeather Notifications: Receive notifications for weather changes and alerts.\n\nWhy Choose Our App?\n\nAccuracy: Our app uses reliable weather data sources to provide accurate forecasts.\nUser-Friendly: Easy-to-use interface for effortless navigation and information access.\nCustomization: Tailor the app to your preferences with customizable settings.\nMulti-Language Support: Available in multiple languages for a global user base.\nFeedback: We value your feedback and continuously strive to improve the app.\n\nContact Us:\n\nIf you have any questions, feedback, or suggestions, please feel free to reach out to us at support@weatherapp.com. Your input helps us enhance your weather experience.\n\nThank you for choosing our weather app. Stay informed and stay prepared!"
            android:textSize="16sp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"/>

    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>